<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on MultiForM - Multiscale Fluid Dynamics and Porous Media</title>
    <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on MultiForM - Multiscale Fluid Dynamics and Porous Media</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.multiform.xyz/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our new PhD students</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/robertdylan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/robertdylan/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our new PhD students Robert and Dylan:
 Robert Barnett will work on a project related to the multiscale modelling and simulation of charged particles in porous media and lithium-ion batteries, supervised by Matteo Icardi and John King (Mathematics). Adilan Mahdiyasa &amp;ldquo;Dylan&amp;rdquo; will work on the modelling and simulation of peatlands and their effect on carbon storage, supervised by David Large, Bagus Muljadi (Engineering), and Matteo Icardi (Mathematics).  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th InterPore UK conference</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/2019interporeuk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/2019interporeuk/</guid>
      <description>Sept 2-3 2019, Teeside University. Call for abstract is open!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Nottingham OpenFOAM(R) workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/2019openfoam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/2019openfoam/</guid>
      <description>July 22-23 2019 at the University of Nottingham. Registration is open!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New MultiForM website</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/website/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our brand new website, created with the great Hugo, hosted on GitHub.
Here are relevant links if you want to know how this website works:
 GitHub pages Namecheap Hugo GoHugo Ananke theme Mmark markdown interpreter Katex  The Ananke theme has been modified to enable $\LaTeX$ through Mmark and Katex. Here is an example of maths&amp;rsquo; rendering
[ \int_{a}^{b} x^2 dx ]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASCE EMI 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/asce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/asce/</guid>
      <description>2020 International Conference of the Engineering Mechanics Institute
April 5-8
Durham, UK
Details for the conference can be found in the conference website. The deadline for submission of abstracts is the 15th of November, 2019.
Minisymposium Organizers
 Matteo Icardi, The University of Nottingham Savvas Triantafyllou, The University of Nottingham Emilio Martínez-Pañeda, Imperial College London  MS-52: Analysis and Methods for the Simulation of Deformation, Failure and Coupled Processes Across Scales</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WCCM ECCOMAS 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/eccomas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.multiform.xyz/post/eccomas/</guid>
      <description>14th World Congress on Computational Mechanics and 8th European Congress on Computational Methods in Applied Science and Engineering
Paris, July 19-24 2020
MS292: NOVEL MODELLING AND NUMERICAL APPROACHES FOR FLOW AND TRANSPORT PROCESSES IN POROUS MEDIA
Organisers
 Marco Berardi, CNR Mario Putti, Padova Matteo Icardi, Nottingham Bagus Muljadi, Nottingham  Details about the conference can be found here The deadline for submissions is December 15, 2019.
Description
Porous media are ubiquitous in many industrial and natural processes, and there is a growing need of understanding and predicting the multiscale flow and transport phenomena in key energy and manufacturing sectors such as subsurface reservoirs, vadose and root zones, composite materials, filtration, and catalytic reactors, just to name a few.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>